# **SUMMARY**

Smart and motivated Information Technology Support Specialist with over 10 years of progressive experience in providing client service support and resolving level 2 escalations via break/fix analysis and problem determination. Bachelor of Science in Computer Information Systems with concentration in Security. Strong aptitude for learning new technologies. Adept in effective communication, team collaboration, flexibility, and leadership with a solid understanding of Chain of Command.

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

	_			
•	Ser	1/10	$\triangle N$	OW
•	OCI	VIU	CIV	OVV

- Active Directory
- Bomgar Cloud
- Software Center
- Sailpoint IAM
- C\C++
- C#
- Python
- Java

- HTML5
- CSS3
- SQL
- .NET
- ASP.NET
- Sqlite
- Microsoft Access
- Bloodshed Dev C
- Notepad++

- Eclispe
- Netbeans
- Visual Studio
- Dreamweaver
- Unity
- SonarQube
- TortoiseSVN
- Git
- Bash

## **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor of Science in Computer Information Systems** *DeVry University* 

June 2013

Downers Grove, IL

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Software Engineer, Sr.

Lockheed Martin

Sep 2019 – Present

Nov 2018 - Sep 2019

King George, VA

• Team Lead for the Dahlgren site in coding applications utilizing Unity and the C# programming language.

### **Information Technology Support Engineer**

Charlotte. NC

American Express Global Business Travel

- People: Provide top tier customer service, remote technical service support, installation, configuration and problem resolution.
- Passion: Show enthusiasm to coordinate support and repair activities with other teams with a winning attitude.
- Progress: Monitor and update help desk incident tracking tickets to see actions through from end to end to deliver satisfying results.

Systems Services Engineer International Business Machines

Jan 2016 – Nov 2018 Research Triangle Park, NC

- Perform backups/restorals, and hardware/software installs, moves, adds, and changes.
- Resolve problem tickets in a timely manner in accordance with service level agreement (SLA) and follow established escalation procedures.
- Interact with end users to ensure satisfaction following established procedures to deliver superior service by going above and beyond to tackle assignments outside of normal duties.
- Exemplified outgoing personality and work ethic by extending work hours to assist SCCM team with image testing to meet deadline provided by American Express Global Business Travel, (2018).
- Volunteered to travel to Tampa, FL to assist American Express Global Business Travel depot operations team to catch up on imaging and shipping PC's after hurricane put them behind schedule, (2017).
- Volunteered for IBM transitions team and assisted with migrating Truven Health over to IBM Watson and ensured end users could access IBM resources over VPN, (2016).

# Field Services Engineer

Jan 2015 - Jan 2016

**OC Communications** 

Sacramento, CA

• Performed onsite troubleshooting/technical support for cable services (video, internet, and voice) for Comcast residential subscribers, and trained customers on how to use cable services.

# Information Technology Helpdesk Engineer Colfax Fluid Handling

Jun 2013 - Jan 2015

Monroe, NC

- Provided technical support and maintained desktop computing environment to include: installed, diagnosed, repaired, maintained, and upgraded all PC hardware and peripherals to ensure optimal workstation performance.
- Spearheaded the IT Asset E-disposal program and reduced inventory by over 25% by disposing outdated equipment.

#### PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATIONS

- (ISC)2 Systems Security Certified Practitioner (SSCP): IAT LEVEL II
- CompTIA Security + CE: IAT LEVEL II
- Scrum.org Professional Scrum Master (PSM) I